{
    "id": "cbba6a347ecb4b7580a011add96ba76e",
    "title": "Complete the sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7d9aa915b38447a5a25c46a0d272bbee",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I want to know ............................... she is angry with me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "why",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If he had asked me, I .................................... him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would help",
                        "would have helped",
                        "will help"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She would have come if you ................................... her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "invited",
                        "had invited",
                        "invite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are looking forward .................................... from you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to hear",
                        "to hearing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "No sooner did we hear the gunshots than we .................................. to the camp.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rushed",
                        "rush",
                        "have rushed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Would you mind ........................................ a bit?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to move",
                        "moving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is very fond ...................................... her grandchildren.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "with",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He enjoys ..................................... in the sea.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "swimming",
                        "to swim"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She accused me ........................................... her dog.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to poison",
                        "for poisoning",
                        "of poisoning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is very confident …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to win",
                        "of winning",
                        "about winning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}